GORDON WATTS

GAME DEVELOPER

OBJECTIVE

Hard-working Computer Science major (3.5 GPA) currently attending University of Central Florida, with 1.5+ years of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of customer satisfaction skills to successfully fill the Game Developer role at your company. Frequently praised as hard-working by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company.

EXPERIENCE

May 2020 - Aug 2020 Insider at Papa John's Jun 2018 - Dec 2019 Shift Leader at Five Guy's

- · Assisted customers with queries using product knowledge.
- Communicated any shift problems to immediate supervisor.
- Worked flexible schedule, including evening and weekend hours.
- Coached employees and maintained physical presence on shift.
- Monitored quality and quantity of output of production lines during course of shift.
- Delivered sales through friendly and efficient customer service.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Adobe Certified Associate in Digital Video (Adobe Premiere Pro)
- Adobe Certified Associate in Digital Video (Adobe Photoshop Pro)
- ServSafe Manager Certification

EXTRACURRICULAR / PROJECTS

- 2021-22 Event Director for Game Dev Knights
- Game Terra Nova

This was my first game completed in a team setting. With it originally starting off in a Game Jam, my team members and I decided to complete the game and soon fully released it on the GameJolt platform.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL FLORIDA

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Computer Science Orlando, FL 3.5 GPA, expected graduation May 2023

EASTERN FLORIDA STATE COLLEGE

Associate of the Arts (A.A.) Melbourne, FL Graduated May 2019

KEY SKILLS

- MANAGEMENT
- GAME DESIGN

TOOLS

- C# LANGUAGE
- C LANGUAGE
- UNITY GAME ENGINE

AWARDS

DEAN'S LIST EFSC 2016-2019

https://gamejolt.com/games/terranova/592282

Game – Space Invaders Clone
This is my first game project made from scratch. Took a few weeks to make, but in that time I learned so much about the game making process. Also challenged my programming skills, and my knowledge of the engine I used, Unity. https://dstroid.itch.io/space-invaders-clone

REFERENCES

Available on request.